A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Lord Death has made his decision.
This afternoon, you'll begin class on a trial basis.
I'll come to get you later on, so be sure you're ready.
You hear me?
Still nothing.
Look, I'm a zombie and I still teach classes here.
So surely someone who's still alive can make a good student.
Hello in there.
Hello.
This kid totally hates me.
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
6人目も合わさず運命まで絡んでく
行き先もらったポテル 食えない夜を恥で
不可愛しすぎた眩しさが 悪い夢に続いても
繋いだ魂の火が胸を刺すなら
言葉よりもっと強い響きが今聞こえるか
出会った訳は途絶びに 惹きつけられて
触れた瞬間の傷の分だけ確かになれる
I was talking to him for a long time trying to persuade him to come out but he was too afraid
in the end he told me that because I was a zombie he didn't know how to deal with me
okay I see he's incredibly depressed and I can't think what else to do
his room's down that way so I finally get to see Krona you seem to have found some way to connect to and understand his soul wavelength I'd like you to teach him some things so he can become more accustomed to the academy it's no problem I'm happy to help out thank you
no she finally showed up take her around the school too while you're at it
I'm just walking in circles where am I supposed to go
Sid it's you pardon me a second I was so lost I thought I was gonna die here
you used to go to this school too Marie
the exciting and embarrassing trial enrollment the DWMA new lifestyle support fair is open
Krona the demon swordsman a legacy of madness left by the witch Medusa who created a new form of weapon and meister when she melted down the demon sword Ragnarok mixed him into black blood and used that blood to replace Krona's own
a witch's soul is needed to turn a magic weapon into a death site in the end perhaps it is the witch who is responsible for the evolution of the weapon and not the weapons Meister
you can't stand it can you stop why hold it in that's not healthy you want to dismember everything you can't hide it from me
you're curious about him you want to study the child I created
you've been infected by the Kishin's madness I can't wait to see what happens
coming in hey there's no one here
Maka
what are you doing over there I feel safer when I'm tucked in the corner like this
come on you look like somebody's given you a time-out here stand up yeah okay
I'm going to show you around the Academy today
oh you are I don't know you know I'm really happy to have you here Krona
yeah
hey hey
and this lady is Miss Marie
I'm new here too
well I'm new as a teacher anyway tomorrow is my first day
I know how you feel Krona we're in the same boat
but don't worry I'm sure we'll both do just fine
oh okay oh I see now show him he's not alone a nice technique Marie
Kona the blue man is back again he scares me
Sid we need you to stay out here
you can relax I know Sid there looks like a big scary blue gorilla
but I promise he's actually a pretty nice guy
hey all right then we don't want to keep your education waiting anymore now do we
let's get going I wouldn't be getting too cocky now if I were you stupid humans
hi there mini Ragnarok
oh what is that it's so cute
what'd you do to me you ugly cow
I don't know what you mean
what are you doing here I never agreed to be your friend
aww
I'm feeling so much closer to you now that you can't hurt me
you don't have much to look at under there do you cow
I'm sorry I'm so sorry I didn't mean to I'll never do it again
no Krona it's okay I'm the one who should apologize
come on Krona quit hiding there's nothing to be afraid of here
Come on, Crona, quit hiding.
There's nothing to be afraid of here.
It's so bright.
What?
Why are you laughing?
Did I say something funny?
Well, how do you like our humble academy so far?
Do you think you can get used to being here?
No, this place is definitely not for me.
You're just a little nervous.
You'll be fine, don't worry.
Uh-uh, I can't deal with this.
I want to go back to my corner.
Maybe a nice hard kick would help.
Down, boy.
Oh, hey, I know.
Why not write some poetry?
How does that sound?
Poetry?
You've got to be kidding me.
I write poems a lot when something's bothering me.
It really helps.
Oh, come on.
How much more emo can you possibly get?
You can talk to me if something's wrong, you know?
Why don't we try writing a poem together?
If you say so, I guess I can give it a try.
Are you all done?
Yeah.
I want to see.
This is so stupid.
So, uh, how is it?
Huh?
This makes me wish I'd never been born.
It's so sad.
Hiya, guys!
What are you lame-os doing in here?
The weather's amazing.
We shouldn't be locked up in school.
Let's get going.
Well, I guess it does get gloomy without Blackstar around.
But fear not, now that I'm here.
The sun has come out from behind the clouds.
Read this.
I wish I'd never been born.
What's so horrible about a stupid poem?
I wish that I'd never been born.
I wish that I'd never come back to life.
What the hell, Sid?
When did you get in here?
Uh, about Krona.
There are still some issues to work out.
But I do think you'll get accustomed to the Academy eventually.
Oh, good.
I'm glad to hear it.
But you're looking a little pale, Sid.
Do you think you're coming down with something?
No, no.
No, it's nothing.
Anyway, Krona is headed for the Czech Republic right now.
I sent him along as part of Maka's supplementary lesson.
Why?
What's wrong over there?
There's a village where the citizens spend their time creating figures known as golems.
Apparently, the oldest golem made there has suddenly gone berserk and begun destroying things.
Luckily, the damage so far seems to be light.
Hold on a sec.
Are you for real, Sid?
For real about what?
When golems are created, they are programmed to be protectors.
Whether the damage is light so far or not, the implications here are serious.
For a golem to lose control and begin destroying things is unthinkable.
It may have something to do with the madness wavelengths.
Sid, contact Stein.
This could be very important.
I'd like to hear his opinion on the matter.
So, this is Loof Village, huh?
They sure do have a lot of chimneys.
That's because they make so many golems here.
There's probably a kiln in every house.
Now let's eat us some souls.
Things have changed.
That isn't how we operate anymore.
We're going to do things differently now that we're students at the academy.
I wonder where the supposedly berserk golem that we need to find is hiding.
I'll ask the villagers for details.
These golem creators are enchanters.
They use those giant gloves of theirs to mix magic into the soil.
That's how they create the figures and bring them to life.
I can't say they look all that happy to see us in their village.
Sol!
No one I talk to knows anything about the golem.
They're hiding something, that's for sure.
Hey, you guys.
I'm guessing you're here because you heard about our incident.
You're looking for the golem, the one that's gone berserk.
My name's Giriko.
I'm an enchanter.
I'll show you the way, just follow me.
I'm going to let go.
I'm going to find out.
I have to?
What are you doing sitting here in the dark?
Hey, Stein?
Hey, do you hear me?
Marie.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What do you need?
I have a message from Lord Death.
Apparently, the oldest golem in Loof Village has gone crazy.
Do you have any cups? I'll make us some tea.
Use those over there.
You put tea in a beaker?
Anyway, Lord Death wants to hear your opinion on the subject.
Is this incident going to be a problem for us?
Golems are usually constructed to protect against evil.
It isn't in their programming to become destructive like this.
I suppose modern technology could be used to create golems with different programming.
But then again, you said this happened to the oldest golem they have in the village.
You think the madness wavelengths have something to do with it?
Even if they do, the order of events seems strange.
How do you mean?
Thankfully, as far as we know, there still haven't been any incidents related to the Kishan's revival and madness.
It's hard to believe that the first such incident would involve a soulless creature like the golem going crazy.
I agree. If anything, it seems like people should be the first to be affected by it.
So the first event we hear about shouldn't involve an object like the golem.
That's right. The golem shouldn't go berserk until the world is fully enveloped in the madness of the Kishan.
Of course, we still shouldn't take the situation too lightly.
Hold on a sec.
I'm going to the library.
Please ask Lord Death to give me some time to consider what's happened.
And after all that work to make us tea.
Hey, how much further do we have to go until we reach the golem?
We're almost there.
Yeah, right. That's what you keep telling us.
You and your village are really starting to creep me out, dude.
Be quiet, soul. There's no need to be rude.
The villagers here make their living by creating golems and exporting them to other countries.
The golems ward off evil if you put them by your front door.
You see, everyone is afraid of the unknown.
So what you're trying to say now is that we're evil?
Why are you getting so angry with them? He never said anything like that.
Not in so many words, maybe, but that's what they're thinking.
The truth is we want to live in peace and quiet.
We don't like it much when strangers come to our village.
Which is why we try to adopt the calm of the golem and avoid conflict.
In the end, everyone is the same.
We all have evil inside us.
Even someone who wears a mask of goodness can still have pitch darkness in his heart, you see.
What was that?
Oh, come on. If I tell you, that'll spoil all the fun.
Oh, well. I suppose there's no hiding the truth anymore.
Heads up, soul.
Yeah, I'm already on it.
Impossible. That's crazy.
What's up, Maka?
What's going on?
Golems aren't supposed to be living things, are they?
But I can sense a soul wavelength coming from that thing.
You're a young meister, I take it.
Looks like you figured it out.
I've been waiting for this moment for 800 years.
I use techniques I learned as an enchanter to swap my memories with my own children,
passing my brain through the generations.
I've lived out 30 boring lives.
800 years?
What are you talking about?
The idea was to store up enough strength to take on death.
And his precious organization.
Your DWMA.
But that's all over now.
I think you children might want to start saying your goodbyes.
What the hell is he?
You see, I don't need a meister.
The golem I created for myself will do just fine.
This guy's a weapon?
And his golem has a soul.
What else is wrong with this village?
Give up your attack and turn away right now.
If you do continue to fight me, then I'll take your soul.
You got it?
My engine isn't even running yet.
His wavelength is distorted.
It's full of bloodlust.
Now that I'm good and fired up, there'll be no stopping us.
My soul's wavelength holds 800 years of anger and hatred.
I've been wearing this same forced smile on my face for generations.
I had to be nice to stay under the Academy's radar.
My life so far has been nothing but meaningless crap.
Boring, empty crap.
My life is a pointless cesspool!
Mako!
Dammit.
Smiling so long, I don't remember what my real self is like.
Tell me who I am again.
Think, think, think.
It's got to be in there somewhere.
Oh, yeah.
I think I may have it now.
Everything I am, everything I've made myself into has to go.
It's got to be destroyed.
I'll obliterate it all.
That golem is too big for me to fight effectively.
I know I need to attack it from a distance.
Except I don't know how to do that using a sight.
There is Krona's screech arrow, you know.
Just thought I'd mention that.
Don't know why, though.
We're onlookers.
No way we're gonna help you.
Not even for three pieces of candy.
Ragnarok.
Then how about four?
It was just a figure of speech.
I don't actually want any candy at all.
I'm not a baby, you idiot.
Six pieces, okay?
It's not a matter of number.
Fifteen, then.
I'll give you as many candies as you want.
Really?
Pucka, Alborn.
You know how to strike a good bargain.
It pays to negotiate, don't you think?
The first speed setting doesn't tear him to pieces?
Well, that's disappointing.
Don't underestimate my black blood!
How did I ever manage to fight that thing?
I'm real glad he's on our side now.
Now, Ragnarok.
You seem a little shorter than you used to be.
Sure you can handle this?
Quit your worrying, dumbass!
Don't hurt, Maka, anymore.
If something's bothering you, why not write a poem?
We can write one together, okay?
Here we go, Maka.
Right.
Let's go, Maka.
I wish I'd never been born.
I wish I'd never come back.
I wish I could learn how to enjoy sushi.
I wish I didn't have a hole in my head.
I wish I wasn't hot-tempered.
I wish I didn't have blue skin.
I wish I didn't have fat ankles.
I wish I didn't have bad breath.
Yeah, we all wish that.
On the next episode of Soul Eater,
800 years of bloodlust,
advent of the heretic witch.
Watch it, or you'll wish you had.
But fuck it, I wish I did.
決 of the okay with my life.
In the next episode of Soul Eater,
a treatment of Earline.
I should deny my móvil or a dog.
Of course it may have a little bit,
let's say you may feel what looks like.
I wish I did.
You're lucky to do that.
And that's why.
You know the congress Yeshua.